https://www.okiok.com/cookie-usage-policy/

Penetration Testing & Vulnerability Assessment
Identity Compliance as a Service (ICAAS)
Penetration Testing & Vulnerability Assessment
Identity Compliance as a Service (ICAAS)
Cookie usage Policy
This Website uses cookies to improve the user experience and ensure that it is functioning effectively.
In order to provide you with a more personalized and responsive service we need to remember and store information about how you use this website. This is done using small text files called cookies. Cookies contain small amounts of information and are download to your computer or other device by a server from this website. Your web browser then sends these cookies back to this website on each subsequent visit so that it can recognize you and remember things like your user preferences.
Whenever you use this website, information may be collected using cookies and other technologies. By using this website, you agree to our use of cookies as described in this Cookie usage policy.
Collected information and usage
We collect and store information, including personally identifiable information (“personal information”), that is voluntarily supplied to us by you when registering or when using our Website. Some information, such as your e-mail accounts and credentials, e-mail account contents and e-mail address(es), are required from you to be able to use various forms. You can choose not to use the forms requests. We use personal information to deliver the services and relevant information to you, to improve our Website and service delivery, and to develop analytics and aggregated data that allow us to utilize and enhance our Website and related services.
The personal data provided by you may be used to communicate with you in connection with your various inquiries and will be kept for the time period in which it is necessary for the purpose it was collected.
We may also collect and store non-personally identifiable information that is automatically generated when you use our Website or related services. We may use the resulting non-personally identifiable information, such as your browser version, IP address, referring domains, pages visited, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, the nature of your use of the Website and cookie information, to improve our Website and services delivery, including advertising, and to develop analytics and aggregated data that allow us to utilize our Website and services and reach out to you via our Website and services. Such data may be used to analyze trends, to manage the Website, to track your movements around the Website and to gather demographic data about our visitors. The data gathered by these cookies is in the form of aggregated data and remain anonymous.
Information disclosure to third parties
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to third parties your personal information without your consent. However, we may disclose personal information in situations described below:
We may disclose your personal information to authorized agents who are employed by us to perform tasks on our behalf and need to use this information to provide products and services to you. Unless we communicate with you differently, our authorized agents do not have the right to use any personal information we share with them beyond what is required to provide the product or the service to you. In this context, you consent to the sharing of your personal information for these purposes.
The information provided allows us to ensure compliance with our terms and conditions applicable to the provided products and services, the various laws and regulations or to protect our rights, intellectual property and the security of our services.
In the course of acquisition or transfer of intellectual property, your non-personal information and your personal information may be transferred to the new owner, provided that the terms of this statement continue to apply.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may disclose your personal information to third parties with your consent. You will be notified when your personal information is shared, and you will be able to withdraw your authorization at any time.
We may also provide non-personally identifiable information, or aggregated information that does not identify you, to other parties, such as Google Analytics, for analytics, marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Computer Logs
We may use logs to collect data about visitors’ use of the Website. We may review server logs for security purposes, for example, to detect intrusions into our network. Server log data, which contains visitors’ IP addresses, could in instances of criminal malfeasance be used to trace and identify individuals. In such instances, raw data logs would be shared with appropriate investigative bodies authorized to investigate such breaches of security. Like cookies, logs do not cross reference the data automatically collected with any type of personal data that is voluntarily offered by you on or through this Website.
Links to non-OKIOK websites and third-party applications
This Website may contain links to third-party websites and third-party applications that are not affiliated with OKIOK (such as Google for Maps, ShareThis for social sharing, Twitter and Facebook feeds, and more). We do not in any way endorse or make any representations about such third-party websites and applications. As such, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such third-party websites and applications that are subject to their own privacy policies. If you choose to access such links, we encourage you to review all third-party site privacy policies before submitting any of your data.
Security measures to protect personal data
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. In this context, best practices in information security are implemented by us and our hosting providers.
It should be noted that we cannot be held responsible for any personal data you share or post on public spaces, such as our blogs. Such public spaces may be consulted or viewed by anyone visiting our Website and, as such, falls outside the scope of this notice.
OKIOK reserves the right to make changes to this Notice from time to time without notice.
RAC/M Identity: Optimize Identity Governance & Administration | OKIOK
Services
Penetration Testing & Vulnerability Assessment
Identity Compliance as a Service (ICAAS)
Strategic Consulting & Expertise On Demand – Cyber Security
Computer Forensics | Identify and Preserve Electronic Evidence | OKIOK
Governance and Compliance | Risk Management | GRC | OKIOK Services
RAC/M, RAC/M Identity, S-Filer, S-Filer Portal, S-Filer Cloud and Percutio are registered trademarks of OKIOK Data ltd.
All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
© 2018 OKIOK.
Contact Us
We're not around right now. But you can send us an email and we'll get back to you, asap.
Not readable? Change text.
I consent to Okiok collecting my details through this form.
Send
Start typing and press Enter to search
